Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Yes, I'm glad you enjoyed the show!
Good evening, everyone. The morning brown eyes are upon us.
We are Sulte Art Studies.
Before we start the show, we would like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for your favorite one or two.
The person who has the number card with the number written on it is today's MC.
Okay, let's have it.
Yes, I'll hold it.
It's dangerous. I can see it.
You can see it.
Let the voting begin!
What do you think? Yuna, do you have an MC in the showroom?
Oh, no.
But this is my third time today,
I've been on all of them with Emma.
I've been with Emma for all of them. I told you before.
Have I ever done anything with you? Me.
What?
No, I haven't.
Don't tell me you can see me.
I'm sorry.
I can see you.
Okay, let's shuffle it around.
Shuffled.
Yes, you did. Okay, I'm gonna have my dad shuffle it around a little bit.
I'll get to it.
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's it.
Number two?
Number two.
Okay, here we go.
Ready!
So, today, you are Yuna, right?
Yes, that's right. Well, I'm Yurina Nakamura, and I'll be your MC today.
I will do my best.
Please do your best.
Can I introduce myself?
Is it me? I'm sorry. My number is 16.Is it me? I'm sorry. My attendance number is 16.
I am Uma Sakurai. Pleased to meet you.
Well, let's begin.
Ebichu's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom
Yay!
Today is the 60th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom.
Thank you very much for visiting Ebitu's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom.
Thank you very much.
Ebichu's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom is the sister show of our sister showroom, Ukka-san's Showroom.
You can get the original avatar of EBITCHU SHOWROOM by registering to our showroom,
You can get it for free or for a fee by guesting.
Would you like to see the avatar?
It's amazing!
It's so red!
It's so red! Today.
It's full of them.
Ella wants to make one of these, too.
I want to make one too.
Yes, I do. So here is the time to spread the word.
In order for as many people as possible to see this distribution, I'm going to tweet about it on the Ebichu Twitter now, so please tweet about it.
Okay.
What do you say? Peace?
Peace?
Thank you very much.
Okay, everybody. I'm going to make an announcement now,
Please take notice.
Please notice me.
Okay, so today we're going to do a project like this. It's called "The Hilarious and Irrelevant Questionnaire Talk.
Before the talk, we will take a questionnaire to decide what to talk about.
Let's start with the theme of the talk. Here are the themes for today's talk.
(1) Report on the tour and impressions
2) Familien 2023 report
3) Summer Glitter distribution release
4) Overnight stay, Niko-chan, and Emina
⑤Ebay na Kyoto
(6) Emibina's first anniversary will be coming soon
I'm all about eyebrows.
I've only talked about eyebrows.
Then, please vote.
I want to talk about Familen, don't you?
That's right. It's the closest.That's right. That's the closest you've been.
A recent story.
What will it be?
I wonder.
The Emayuna Festival.
Emayuna Festival.
There are so many themes for Emayuna's talk,
It's endless.
It's all about Emayuna, even though it could be a personal story.
It's more about Emayuna than about myself.
Yes.
Five, four, three, two, one, done!
Yay!
Let's see the result.
If it's number 4...
Yes.
Number one is four, number four is three.
Four?
Is it 4? Because I'm still curious.
I see.
The neighbor, this is me,
I stayed at Yunan's house during the rehearsal for Famien,
This is an incident that took place during that time,
We wanted to have dinner together,
We decided to order ramen noodles and said we would Uber,
We Ubered and YoonA ordered it for us,
We were both very hungry,
Fried rice set.
Fried rice and ramen,
We also ordered fries and gyoza on the side.
I think now that we ordered a lot,
When it arrived, there were two bags,
They were huge.
They were huge. I wondered why.
I wondered why,
First of all, there were two bags of ramen noodles,
And in the same bag, there were fries and gyoza (dumplings) on the side.
What? What's the other one? I thought,
I looked and found another bag of the exact same ramen,
What? This? For three people? I looked at my order history.
I looked at my order history, and I don't know if Yuna was tired or sleepwalking,When I looked at the order history, I don't know if Yuna was tired or sleepwalking, but she ordered ramen for three people,
I don't know if she was tired or sleepy, but she ordered ramen for three people,
That was a surprise to me, so I thought I'd share it with you,
I thought I'd share it with you all.
I wanted to share it with you because the other ramen I bought was a fried rice set,
So there was another large amount of fried rice.
I couldn't eat this one.
Somebody, right?
For three people.
All carbs.
Indeed.
But I was tired because of rehearsals and such.
You are tired.
Something Yuna told me,
When you are tired, you make choices.
It's like people have a limited number of choices in a day.
So, if you make too many choices at the beginning, you will be tired. If you make too many choices in the beginning, you don't have the ability to make choices in the latter half,
In the second half of the day, we don't have the ability to make any more choices,
So, we have to be very careful with the choices we make.
So we were at the Famille rehearsal,
Next was this side of the aisle. This way. I couldn't choose anymore,
So you couldn't choose ramen anymore, right?
That's right.
That's how it is.
You actually said you could have any kind of ramen.
He said he would eat anything as long as he could eat it.
We couldn't really choose, but we did our best to choose ramen,
But we ordered enough for three people.
We couldn't finish it. As expected.
As expected. We couldn't finish it.
Because I opened one bag and two ramen noodles came out already,
I was so scared of what was in the other bag.
I was scared.
I was like, "What is this?
I was really scared.
I was so surprised.
That's what I call it.
Let's move on.
Okay.
Let's go one more time,Okay, one more time,
Representative, please.
I wonder what would be good. I wonder what everyone wants to hear.
I wonder what they want to hear. I don't know...but...2...or...2...is it...2...is it...2...
I think it's 2, 2 is the one. Why doesn't everybody vote for 2?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Ding-dong. End.
What?
What? Oh, everyone voted for 2 next time.
Okay, let's go to the Pamien 2023 debriefing.
Here's the set list for Pamien 2023.
What do you think? How was your first Famien? It was fun.
What impressed you? The amount of water.
That's for sure. It was amazing.
There was some kind of deep-fried prawns with a cannon-like device that sprayed water all over the audience,
I think it was the second day, and the wind was blowing this way on the second day.
It was blowing this way, and I was spraying water this way, so it all came back to me,
I was like, "Oh yeah, that was really fun. That was a lot of fun.
So it was fun. It was fun.
It was good.
What about Eva?
I think the one that I really enjoyed was Made in Japan sometime ago.
It was really fun.
It was the first time to have a Yagura, we didn't have one last year,
I had a lot of fun to go back there this year,
It was also really fun to be able to go back up there and be close to my family.
When we went for a run, for example.
I was really happy to be close to them, but I was desperate to get there,
But I was singing so hard to get there,
I was running with my head straight,
Was it embarrassing?
It was very embarrassing.
It was embarrassing.
I was running, you know, and he had this look on his face,
I was so embarrassed because he was so close to me that I couldn't make eye contact with him the whole time.
You know. Just like Luna in the mission.
It was amazing.
But I was thinking about the night at Famien, the first day was at Sanrio.
That was fantastic.
The fireworks were amazing.
The fireworks were great. The fireworks were great, too,Fireworks were terrible. Fireworks were bad,
The full sign was terrible.
It was terrible.
When we had the Nachumero Rendezvous, the fireworks went off,
They weren't moving anymore.
They were just chu-chu-chu-chu-chu.
All the time. It really bothered me.
Going around while tut-tutting?
It was so much fun to go around the perimeter,
I wanted to do that. I wanted to walk around like this,
I wanted to do it like this, but I wanted to walk around with the staff.
I really saw it, didn't I? Even though we were first-timers.
We noticed when we went to the center stage,
Honma was up from somewhere in the first row.
Really?
Homma was up there too, just without realizing it.
I didn't know that.
That makes me furious.
Really?
He said it's really great to see fireworks with Ebichu.
That makes me happy.
I know.
I understand.
It really was the most fun I've had in 15 summers.
It was really fun.
Also, the family complex,
We also added new songs like "Family Complex" and "Festival Chua" this time,
We also have new lyrics with our names on them.
How was it? How did you like it?
How did you like it?
I really liked the NES name part,
The new part after Yuna's. I was so nervous the first time I sang it,
I was so nervous when I sang the first part.
But you know, I like everyone's part in Emilea,
I thought Yuna's part was really stylish.
She sang with a very stylish style.
It's nice because it's a little different from the previous parts.
Three.
But I was surprised by the festival tour.
I've been listening to it backstage for a long time,
I've been listening to it backstage,I've been listening backstage the whole time,
Even after I said the first No. 3,
The volume of the calls was amazing.
It was like "Maya Ma!
It was like a huge boom.
That's for sure. It was a lot of fun to hear the calls.
I was also surprised when I heard her name was Yuna-chan.
That's for sure. I'm so happy.
I wanted a three-letter nickname for the festival.
Something like, "A-match.
But I couldn't get one in the end.
I wonder what it is. Nakamura-san is a good match for me.
When I left, Nakamura-san is so disjointed that someone would make a fool of himself.
That's true.
I get an "ah-ha" feeling.
Even Ya-san.
Oh, that's true.
Ya-san is good.
Ya, you're good.
Well, it's already done, but it's a sound source.
Yes, it is.
But I personally like Nakkamu.
It's the first time I've ever heard you say "what is it?
Isn't it kind of nice?
Nakkamu.
Maybe it should have been Yuna instead of Yuna-chan.
Ah, Yuna-san. Yuna-san.
You know, Emma often calls me Yuna-san.
I call her Yuna-san.
Surprisingly, you two are not Emma and Yuna.
I never call her Emma either.
It's unexpected, isn't it?
Emma-chan, Emma-san.
You call me Emma-chan, Emma-san, Emma-chan, Emma-chan.
We had dinner together today,
She called me Emachisato,
I don't know, you don't say Emma Yuna, right?
You don't say that, do you?
You don't talk about the Famie.
That's right. I'm sorry.
It was fun at Famien, wasn't it? I want to do it again.That was fun Famien. I want to do it again.
Summer Gritta was also performed for the first time.
How was it, everyone?
I don't know.
I don't know. It's still playing now.
Oyakaki Babe.
Your English is great. It was difficult.
But, Mr. Sakurayama, isn't your English pronunciation great?
Oh, thank you very much.
It was pronounced like ECC.
It was pronounced just like ECC.
It was great to see it live.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy to see it live,
E-E-E-E-Y-E-Y.
The rap music is great, isn't it?
Your rap is great, too.
Riko's.
It's nice, isn't it?
But after I reach out like this.
Riko's makeup looks really cool.
That's for sure.
At that time, since Ema and I are new
I laugh when my eyes are really wide.
There are so many new faces.
So many.
Also, what do you like about Ema?
I like the way you hold hands here.
Holding hands like this.
I hold hands like this until I see Hamin's day.
Why did I say make-up?
I don't know.
I can't hold hands because I'm holding the microphone here,
So we danced to the rhythm of hearts.
I was just walking along.
Then Kabuki-sensei told me that we didn't seem to get along with each other.
I only had a little bit, so Yuna was doing it like this at first,
I was holding it like this, but the dance teacher said, "You're getting in the way,
But it looks like the dance teacher is asking me to move out of the way.
Yuna, I'm taking it home.Yuna, I'm bringing it back.
They said it would look like I was doing that,
So when Yuna sang on the microphone, we decided to bring it back and connect it properly.
It was difficult at first.
It was difficult.
I had never danced before, and it was really cool,
We danced together many times until we got it into our bodies.
We did it.
We did it so many times.
What do you think? What do you think?
I also liked the summer deja vu.
Summer déjà vu and the happy wire jab. I was doing that feeling.
It's good.
It's nice.
I have a lot to say, but I personally liked the costumes.
The first one, the school uniform-style outfit, was really cute.
The tie here and the backs of the sleeves were all colored,
It was really cute.
The goldfish was cute too.
The goldfish was cute.
The towels used for the summer déjà vu were like towels made from the material of the goldfish costumes,
It was really cute.
It was so cute.
It was cute.
What do you guys like?
Which one did they like?
Even the goldfish was cute.
She was cute.
I was already crying when she said "I want to seduce you..." after the audition,
I want to seduce you.
I feel like this is the second time I've joined the group.
I'm sure. Maybe I didn't do that much.
I hadn't done it before.
It was fresh.
It reminded me of something. I remember a lot of things.
Yes, that's right!
This is the theme of another talk, so let's take some pictures.
Let's film it.
He said he's going to take pictures.I'll take a picture of it.
I'll take it.
I don't know what the theme of the talk was, but I'll listen to it. Later.
I remembered at the camp.
That's good.
What else?
I was also happy that I got to meet Star da Streit.
It was Matsudaira, wasn't it?
I loved Star da Streit so much,
I loved Star da Streit so much that we did it on the anniversary of his birth.
But it was the first time for 10 of us to do it together, so I was really happy.
And Utamura, too.
Utamura.
Everything was really delicious.
It was delicious.
Did everyone eat? Utamura.
Yuna, what did you eat?
I had a motsu nabe soup,
I had a soup like motsu nabe, and a rice cake with plum shells,
I had scallop skewers.
Chocolate bananas.
Chocolate bananas are so delicious.
I had one too,
It was so cold,
The chocolate banana was really delicious.
I wonder what else it was.
That was delicious. It's like a manju-mo.
It was really good.
I wanted to eat it, but I didn't eat it.
The chocolate banana was really good.
It was really good.
I also ate my own pita bread,
I also had a cheese ball,
It was delicious.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if Ema-chan had anything to eat in the village where she sings.
What?
Emma didn't eat at the Singing Village either.
You didn't eat the Futa-bread or the cheese balls?
No, I didn't. I'm sorry.
What?What?
What? You haven't eaten?
No, I'm not eating.
What? What did you have?
Motsu-nabe soup and umegai mochi (plum sticky rice cake).
I didn't eat either.
I'm just now getting angry with Yuna,
Wait, I didn't eat any of Yuna's food.
That's Mr. Sato.
I'm from the younger members,
I was pretty much the first one to finish the older members' food. All of them.
So I thought I only had enough left for the younger members,
I thought I had finished all of them.
But I didn't eat any of them.
Only mine?
You'll have to do it again next year.
I will. Of course I'll do it again next year.
The pressure is great.
Next year, too.
We sold out of Umegai-mochi.
That's right. I wanted to eat umegai mochi on the first day, but they were sold out,
You know, it's nice to be in a local area,
It's nice to be able to eat famous local specialties, isn't it?
I think you can have umegai mochi in Yamanashi.
I'm sure. It's so fresh.
But I really want you to try the real umegai mochi.
Please eat at Dazaifu Tenmangu.
It's really delicious.
It tastes so good when it's freshly baked.
Then let's go together.
Let's go.
Pitta Dazaar Eftenmang, of course.
Seriously?
I need some feedback on my study.
I see. Then let me go.
I think it's too late to specify now,
Don't worry, you're still in high school. You still have two more years to graduate.
I'm going to graduate.
I'll go to the next specific one.
We've already said everything one-sidedly,We talked one-sidedly about everything,
So you want to hear everyone's memories in the comments.
I'd like to hear them.
Please comment.
Are they here? Lots of them.
I'm here.
I kept going back down,
I've been looking all the way back down, but look at it this way.
It's so wet.
Yeah, it was.
Did you enjoy the second day of heavy rain?
It was fun.
Positive.
But I sang while soaking wet in my nice yukata.
It was nice to get a little emotional.
Indeed. The nice yukata was really nice.
You're tanned and peeled.
Oh, no...
It hurts.
Did you get sunburned? Yuna.
Did you? I did.
I don't know. I don't feel like I got so sunburned.
But on the second day, I forgot to use sunscreen on my hands and feet.
Oh well.
Did I get a little sunburned?
But, you know, they didn't have that much sunburn on the second day.
So I was still fine.
That's good.
Well, did you get burned?
It was totally burnt.
A little burned?
Yes, indeed. Very white.
Karashi.
It was really white.
On the night of the first day, he said he was thrilled to be able to see Mt.
You could see it.
That's for sure.
You saw the digital Mt.
Right. I did. It was a digital projection.
We couldn't see it from our side of the stage,
I could see it on the monitor in the back.I could see it on the monitor behind me, the one the camera guy showed me.
It was raining heavily, but it stopped raining during the concert, so it was really great.
I knew there was a woman with a sunny disposition.
Oh, really?
Isn't Emma amazing?
I feel like I'm going to be fine.
What?
I think Emma is a sunny girl.
It hasn't rained for a long time.
That's for sure. I feel like it never rains when I'm with Emma.
It never rains when I go out with Emma.
Day 2's preamble made me laugh.
Prelude?
The preamble?
The prelude made me laugh.
Yuna-chan and Maeyama-san's hands.
That's right. I can't reach forward.
What?
You think I'm reaching.
But earlier, I took a selfie with Emma,
I took a selfie with Emma, like, "I'm going to do a showroom,
And I couldn't keep my arms away from her.
When I hold her hand, I can't stretch it.
Now I can stretch it,
I know.
Did you talk about that?
Yes, that's right. That's why the camera won't stretch.
Mayama-san was very sharp.
Was she sharp?
He said I was kind of cute,
Then he said, "If it's natural, it's stardust.
That's amazing. That's what I'm talking about.
It was really sharp.
Yeah. It was really sharp.
Po-chan and Riko's machimono imitation was funny.
This is also a prelude.
I wanted to hear it.
At first, Miru-chan talked a lot,
When it came time for self-introductions, all three of us said, "I'm number 16, Sakurayama,
I said, "Attendance number 16, Sakurayama.
That probably amused everyone.That was probably the funniest thing for all of us.
I think I'm starting to sound like them.
They sound alike, don't they?
Like, "How are you doing today? Everyone can imitate it, right?
Yes, they can. Everyone can do it.
Isn't it funny?
It's funny how Emma's expressions change with each show.
I had a feeling.
Emma gets close to me.
How's today?
They all look alike, don't they?
They're cute.
Everyone can do it.
I'm not moving my mouth.
How's today?
I really think I can do non-airplane work.
I'd love to do it sometime.
Famien.
I love that you two were so perfect, it didn't seem like it was your first time.
You did a great job.
I'm glad.
Familien, right? You did a great job on the free.
You did a great job at the Famien,
You said you had a hard time during the spring tour,
It's getting harder and harder.
For the first time, we played four songs in one day.
You did it.
When we did it, the fourth song was fun.
I was kind of weary of it.
It's true that there are times like that.
It was fun.
But I'm glad everyone had a good time.
I'm glad.
I cried during the opening movie.
That's right. Looking back.
Indeed.
The Summer Glitter playing in the background is too scattered and speaks in a relaxed manner.
Let's be crispy.
Let's talk crisply.Let's speak crisply.
Emma.
Don't tell Emma.
She's the one who can't speak the loudest.
When Emma introduced herself to Berryz, the way she said "May the sun shine" was so fucking cute.
Thank you very much.
You said "May it be sunny.
I want you to hear one thing.
What?
I did the Youth Zombies,
They're moving, right?
We're all moving to the right.
Maybe you know it.
You know?
Emma's at the end of the line.
She's actually going to the left. We're all going left.
She was the only one who was happy to go to the right.
Everyone thought that was a bad idea.
Yuno-chan made a face.
It was really frustrating.
Don't worry. I did that too.
Did you?
I got the rhythm of the starting lights wrong.
After only one person finished, everyone started spinning.
It's really written. Yuno-chan was cute because she got the timing of the start light wrong.
You know how you spin it once like this and then spin it again?
She spun while spinning her arms.
Wait for everyone?
Wait. The start light reminded me of something,
I was at rehearsal.
We had rehearsal the next day,
We had rehearsal the next day, and when we were doing Star Dust Light at rehearsal,
It wasn't a very fast dance, and it wasn't a dance that involved my feet,
I broke my leg,
But we were in the middle of a song at rehearsal, so I thought I would not dance,
I thought I wouldn't dance,
I tried to dance as hard as I could, but I just couldn't. It hurt too much,
I tried to dance as hard as I could, but I couldn't. It hurt too much,
I shouldn't laugh, but when I screwed up,
When I realized I had screwed up, I wondered if I would be okay.
After that, I decided to watch it for tomorrow,Then, you know, I thought I'd watch it for tomorrow,
I watched the video I had taken,
I had a bad moment before the B-melody.
So, there is a dance that goes like this,
I saw the video, and I saw that I had a bad fall before the B-melody,
I was so bad at it.
But, until the show,
I had to taping it up properly before the show,
I taped it up properly for the show.
I'm glad I did. Be careful.
Barbastrite on the leg.
It was good at the end, wasn't it? The rehearsal.
That was good.
It's also a memory.
I shouldn't laugh.
But it says Familien that it is funny.
Indeed. That's really true.
Have I said enough about memories?
Have I said enough? Have I heard enough?
Have I heard enough?
Did I hear enough?
I loved Sudden Death, didn't I?
I'm really sorry, but I missed the timing of raising the arm of Ya in Sudden Death.
You said it.
It would have been ideal to say "Hey!
But it was only "Hey! But it was just like "Hey!
That's difficult, isn't it?
You don't know when to say it.
I held it up for about 3 seconds. Oh, that was fast.
You get the hang of it as you go along.
Wouldn't you be surprised if you were listening to Sudden Death and suddenly you were told to do it? I was.
That was fun.
It was super interesting.
It was funny. Because it was.
It was good.
She said the grapes and peaches as souvenirs were delicious.
Yeah, that's what my mom said too.
They went to buy grapes on the way home and said they were delicious.
Really?
She said it was in Yamanashi Prefecture.I said Yamanashi Prefecture.
I knew it was a pear.
I knew I was toying with the idea of pears, didn't I?
Your Japanese is funny, and what you're saying is funny.
It's all strange.
I see... grapes.
But don't they grow pears in Yamanashi?
I think they're famous for pears.
What? I don't know.
I asked him if he didn't think so.
I was told yes.
But they're not famous in Yamanashi.
It's just a name.
"Yamanashi is a treasure house of fruits.
But Fukuoka doesn't have any? Fukuoka has grapes and persimmons, too, I think.
They have everything, even strawberries.
But fruit means fish...
I see.
Okay, let's go to the next theme. Let's go!
Let's vote!
Let's see what we can come up with.
Today is the debriefing.
It's Summer Creator distribution day!
And Emma Yuno
Emma Yuno
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Three.
So, you're going to do it.
Do you see the result?
Isn't it overwhelming?
Overwhelming number 5.
Kyoto, the picture-browed city.
This is what I want to talk about,
You write it as if you said it, but you didn't.
When did I say it? During this busy period.
I write "Kyoto, the city with picturesque eyebrows" as if I have said it, but I haven't said it yet.I wrote "Kyoto, the picture-browed city" as I said, but I haven't said it yet.
I haven't said it yet.
I am talking about wanting to say it.
That's right.
When I was busy learning the choreography recently,
When I was busy learning the choreography, I was like, "Oh my God, I have to do the choreography,
What? He sent me a message saying that he didn't want to go on the trip.
I know.
So I told him I wanted to go to Kyoto.
Right.
You know, I recently posted my latest instagram,
I've been wearing a lot of clothes lately that make me want to go on vacation.
Kyoto and so on and so forth. I'm totally letting my guard down here.
It's nuance. Nuance.
I was posting Instagram while I was on line,
That's right.
I thought I was giving it to you.
That's how much I really want to go.
I want to go.
I want to go to Kyoto.
You are already making plans.
Yes, I have.
I'd like to go that far, but I've already calculated how much I'll spend here and how much I'll spend there,
But I think it's a little bit further away.
A little further.
What do you want to do? In Kyoto.
But I want to go to Arashiyama.
Arashiyama.
I want to eat and walk around.
Kyoto is a city of matches.
I would love to go to Match.
Yuna, did you ever go on a school trip?
I didn't go to Kyoto.
I didn't go to Kyoto. Where did you go?
I went to Hiroshima.
You didn't go to Kyoto?
What?
I want to go.
First time. If you wait, it will be my first time in Kyoto.
It's not my first time in Kyoto.
No, it's not.It's not, man.
Yes, I am.
I'm different, too.
Oh, I want to wear a yukata.
I want to wear a yukata. I want to wear a yukata.
But first, let's go to Asakusa.
Let's go.
I think it's already famous, but it's only in Asakusa.
Asakusa and Anjikin.
Asakusa and only Asakusa.
Let's go. Let's go to Asakusa.
Let's go to Asakusa....we're going to Kyoto first, so it's just a fun thing to keep us going until Kyoto,
Let's go.
Today, we talked about how we would have a lot of fun and enjoy ourselves after the live performance.
That's right.
That's why I've heard so much about Asakusa Ajikin and the like,
Are you done with your report? Are you done with your report? Is your report important? I get a lot of "Is your report important?
But this time, Mr. Nakamura didn't do it either, so I'm fine.
I didn't do it at Asakusa either.
That's right.
I didn't do it, but I was going to go.
That's right. So it's mutual.
So it's both of us. Reports.
I'm working hard on my report,
Don't say "report" when we're talking about Kyoto.
I got mad.
I want to go to Kyoto.
Kyoto is fine, but..,
Anyway, I'd like to go somewhere with just the two of us.
I've never done a report before. I've never done a report or anything.
I've only had dinner, so I'd like to go there.
Today, too,
He said he's going to work hard by today,
We went to a mentaiko noodle shop today.
It was delicious.
It was really good.
I'm glad I got to go there today.
But now the fun is gone again,But now the fun is gone again,
I'll make it again by then, and we'll decide what we're going to do by then.
First of all, I'm looking forward to the big one,
Kyoto.
I have something to work on before then, so I will work on that in Kyoto,
So, I'm looking forward to Kyoto, and I'll do my best until then,
I will make it.
I was not talking about going to Kyoto, but about wanting to go to Kyoto.
That's right.
Sorry about that. Everyone was saying earlier that you haven't been there.
That's great. I left feeling like I had been there.
They said, "Kyoto is hot in summer.
Then, it's definitely that time of the year.
It's winter or fall.
Autumn and winter.
It looks hot in yukata, doesn't it?
Aya and Kariko went to the aquarium together, didn't they?
Yes, we did.
But did Kariko say she wanted to go after seeing that?
She saw that and said she wanted to go, too,
And it's been all over TikTok and Instagram lately,
Maybe it's because it's during the summer vacation period.
So I already want to go.
I want to go.
Let's go.
Kyoto is nice, but I also want to go to Hakone.
That's right. That's what she's saying.
I want to go to Hakone or Nagano.
That's nice.
I want to go to interesting places.
That sounds nice.
Nagano, right? Interesting place.
Yes, it is. Maybe we want to go there.
Let's go.
I want to go.
I heard that the jellyfish corner at the Kyoto Aquarium is beautiful.
Jellyfish are beautiful, aren't they?
Did you know that?
You are a jellyfish?
I didn't know about jellyfish at the Kyoto Aquarium, but I thought they were really beautiful.Jellyfish, I didn't know about the aquarium in Kyoto, but I thought jellyfish were so beautiful.
They are indeed beautiful.
I want to go there.
I want to go.
Let's make plans now.
Let's make plans quickly.
Let's make plans.
Okay.
Can we go already? Next.
Let's go to the next corner.
Next corner?
Yes.
Yes. Next time, mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm GPT.
Yay.
Yay, yay.
Yes.
Have you heard of GPT?
Yes, I have.
It's a service that uses artificial intelligence to instantly answer various questions,
This time, I'd like to do a counterpart to the chat GPT, the EBITCHU GPT.
Yay.
Please feel free to ask us any questions in the comments.
We'll answer it right away anyway.
Yes, I will.
Yuna-san, this is your first time, isn't it?
First time.
What is this?
It's just as it should be, isn't it?
Anyway, it doesn't matter if it's not right, just answer quickly.
I'll have Emo-san answer first.
Oh, that's fine.
Are you okay?
Yes, thanks.
You don't seem very confident.
That's fine.
How many times do you think I've done this?
Okay, Yuna will choose a question at random and answer it when she reads it.
Okay. Oh, just in time.
What is Kyoto's famous food?What is Kyoto's famous food?
Eh, matcha green tea.
Itchy or muuuuchu.
Well, let's try an exchange.
OK.
So, what will you be like 10 years from now?
Ten years from now, Yamachan will be doing something like Inma.
Ten years from now, you will be in a showroom.
Yes.
Is this right?
Yes, it is. It's okay.
So, what did you have for dinner?
Uh, pasta.
Bullshit!
You just said. You just said you had tsukemen.
You had tsukemen.
Gentlemen, I can't believe how sleepy I am. What should I do?
Sleep!
Yes, I'm going to bed.
I'm going to take the next year's Famien back.
Much!
Anyway, hot up hot up hot up.
Nachumelo nachumelo.
I want to do it, but I don't know.
What does GPT stand for in chat GPT?
Going Party Trip.
Oh no!
Oh, I didn't know that. It was pretty messy.
Are there any UFOs?
Yes, there is.
I'm sitting down right now.
What do you recommend when you are tired?
Matcha!
Matcha! It's Kyoto, isn't it?
Before I know it, I'll be answering all of your questions.
That's good.
You like it? Me too.
What's the weather tomorrow?
Cloudy.
Maybe a little bit.It looks a little likely.
But I'm here, so it's fine.
What's the secret to remembering English words?
Write them down!
That's good, that's simple. Write!
What would you do if you met an alien? Shout!
What time would you get up tomorrow? Six o'clock! Early!
That's early! What does the EP stand for?
Let's go to the party!
Okay. See you later.
So that's it. Ebichu GPT, right?
It's fun.
It's fun. It's fun.
Let's master it more.
Let's do our best. Let's work hard. I want to master this too.
Yes, I do. That's all for now.
Yay!
It's the end of the 60th episode of EBITCHU's Delightful and Humuhumuhumuna Showroom in no time.
Then, Mr. Yamamoto, please announce us.
Yes, I will.
Deden!
That's a lot of momentum.
I'm sorry.
Odaiba Adventure King Summer Splash! Awakening Live will be held on August 25.
Please come.
This is Nonaka's birthday.
Birthday.
Soon Nonaka-chan will be 16 years old.
And at Jam Expo 2023 is the day after August 26th.
It will be held at Yokohama Arena, so please come.
So, good bye.
Shiritsu Ebitchigaku 2-man live after school rock'n'roll hyper will be held at Umeda Cypher on September 4 and at Ketty Peppe Haneda with DAISO on September 5.
Please come.
And Maho Sakurai's solo live "Hanie Mile no Mainichi" will be held at Ketty Peppe Yokohama on September 13, so please come and play.
I'll be there!
I hear you all are coming.
I'll be there.
Thank you very much.
Have you already decided? Various.Have you already decided? Various.
I have decided. Various things.
Please look forward to it.
Let's see the top 5 of the final ranking.
Yes.
And pan, Amagami Wow, thank you very much for the leaf sagre degree most accepted 2 aboina animate think it's a boiner!
Thank you for the great work, and thank you for the great work.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good deal on the newest addition to your collection.
And that's the end of the 60th episode of the Hilarious and Funny Showroom in the middle of the day!
We'll let you know as soon as we decide on the next installment, which will be a reflection on what we'll be doing after this.
Awww...
Today's reflection?
Yes.
I am not a good MC after all.
I think I was good. I'm not good at MCing.
I'm not good at MCing, so I'm thinking of having Mr. Sakurai do it from now on.
I will do my best. Together.
I will do my best too.
Yes, I will. So, that's the end of the petit review meeting.
Is it me?
I thought it would be good if I could speak better.
That's true.
I admitted it. I admitted that I am not a good speaker.
That's not true. No, it's not.
I mean, it's mutual.
It's not about Air-chan.
Sure it is.
It's fine. Let's do our best, more than that.
I'll do my best.
It's fine. Be honest.
That's all for now, Sherry and Shrimp Output.
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!